    {
        question: "Which is the only American Football team to go a whole season undefeated, including the Super Bowl?",
        1: "Miami Dolphins",
        2: "Pittsburg Steelers",
        3: "New England Patriots",
        4: "Cleveland Browns",
        correct: "Miami Dolphins"
    }

    {
        question: "What record-setting quarterback was the NFL's 82nd draft pick in 1979?",
        1: "Roger Staubach",
        2: "Terry Bradshaw",
        3: "Johnny Unitas",
        4: "Joe Montana",
        correct: "Joe Montana"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the NFL recors for most sacks in a game?",
        1: "Lawrence Taylor",
        2: "Derrick Thomas",
        3: "Reggie White",
        4: "Michael Strahan",
        correct: "Derrick Thomas"
    }

    {
        question: "Who is the first NFL player ever to play in over 360 games in a career?",
        1: "Gary Anderson",
        2: "Jerry Rice",
        3: "Morten Andersen",
        4: "George Blanda",
        correct: "Morten Andersen"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the NFL record for the most seasons with the same team?",
        1: "Jackie Slater ",
        2: "Emmit Smith",
        3: "Jerry Rice",
        4: "Brett Favre",
        correct: "Jackie Slater "
    }

    {
        question: "Who is the Chicago Cubs fan who interfered with Moises Alou catching a fly ball in 2013?",
        1: "Jeff Cartejena",
        2: "Steve Bartman",
        3: "Donald Trump",
        4: "Kim Kardashian",
        correct: "Jeff Cartejena"
    }

    {
        question: "Which MLB player holds the record for most career home runs?",
        1: "Sammy Sosa",
        2: "Babe Ruth",
        3: "Barry Bonds",
        4: "Hank Aaron",
        correct: "Barry Bonds"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the record for biggest 3 day weight in the Bassmaster Classic?",
        1: "Rick Clunn",
        2: "Randy Howell",
        3: "Jordan Lee",
        4: "Kevin VanDam",
        correct: "Kevin VanDam"
    }

    {
        question: "Who has the most consecutive Bassmaster Classic appearances with 28?",
        1: "Kevin VanDam",
        2: "Rick Clunn",
        3: "Bobby Murray",
        4: "Larry Nixon",
        correct: "Rick Clunn"
    }

    {
        question: "What is the original name of the Houston Astros?",
        1: "Colt .45s",
        2: "Texans",
        3: "Oilers",
        4: "Cougars",
        correct: "Colt .45s"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the Houston Astros record for most home runs in a season?",
        1: "Jose Altuve",
        2: "Jeff Bagwell",
        3: "Craig Biggio",
        4: "Nolan Ryan",
        correct: "Jeff Bagwell"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the NFL career rushing record?",
        1: "Walter Payton",
        2: "Barry Sanders",
        3: "Jim Brown",
        4: "Emmit Smith",
        correct: "Emmit Smith"
    }

    {
        question: "What team did Texas defeat for the 2005 National Title (in the 2006 Rose Bowl)?",
        1: "Notre Dame",
        2: "Florida State",
        3: "USC",
        4: "Alabama",
        correct: "USC"
    }

    {
        question: "What was the Longhorns' game winning streak when the final whistle blew at the 2006 Rose Bowl?",
        1: "22",
        2: "20",
        3: "19",
        4: "21",
        correct: "20"
    }

    {
        question: "What former Texas Longhorn won the Heisman Trophy in 1999?",
        1: "Ricky Williams",
        2: "Colt McCoy",
        3: "Peter Gardere",
        4: "Earl Campbell",
        correct: "Ricky Williams"
    }

    {
        question: "What horse holds the record for the fastest Kentucky Derby time?",
        1: "Secretariat",
        2: "Sham",
        3: "Funny Cide",
        4: "Seabiscuit",
        correct: "Secretariat"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the Texas Longhorn career rushing record?",
        1: "Earl Campbell",
        2: "Cedric Benson",
        3: "Ricky Williams",
        4: "Jamaal Charles",
        correct: "Ricky Williams"
    }

    {
        question: "Who holds the record for most World Series Of Poker bracelets?",
        1: "Phil Ivey",
        2: "Phil Hellmuth ",
        3: "Doyle Brunson",
        4: "Johhny Chan",
        correct: "Phil Hellmuth"
    }

    {
        question: "What NFL team holds the record for most points scored in a game at 72?",
        1: "Dallas Cowboys",
        2: "Pittsburgh Steelers",
        3: "New England Patriots",
        4: "Washington Redskins",
        correct: "Washington Redskins"
    }

    {
        question: "What team was the winner of the longest game in MLB history?(25 Innings)",
        1: "Boston Red Sox",
        2: "Chicago White Sox ",
        3: "New York Yankees",
        4: "Chicago Cubs",
        correct: "Chicago White Sox "
    }

    const questions = ["Who is the Chicago Cubs fan who interfered with Moises Alou catching a fly ball in 2013?",
        "What team was the winner of the longest game in MLB history?(25 Innings)",
        "What NFL team holds the record for most points scored in a game at 72?",
        "Who holds the record for most World Series Of Poker bracelets?",
        "Who holds the Texas Longhorn career rushing record?",
        "What horse holds the record for the fastest Kentucky Derby time?",
        "What former Texas Longhorn won the Heisman Trophy in 1999?",
        "What was the Longhorns' game winning streak when the final whistle blew at the 2006 Rose Bowl?",
        "What team did Texas defeat for the 2005 National Title (in the 2006 Rose Bowl)?",
        "Who holds the NFL career rushing record?",
        "Who holds the Houston Astros record for most home runs in a season?",
        "What is the original name of the Houston Astros?",
        "Who has the most consecutive Bassmaster Classic appearances with 28?",
        "Who holds the record for biggest 3 day weight in the Bassmaster Classic?",
        "Which MLB player holds the record for most career home runs?",
        "Who holds the NFL record for the most seasons with the same team?",
        "Who is the first NFL player ever to play in over 360 games in a career?",
        "Who holds the NFL record for most sacks in a game?",
        "What record-setting quarterback was the NFL's 82nd draft pick in 1979?",
        "Which is the only American Football team to go a whole season undefeated, including the Super Bowl?",
        "What team was the winner of the longest game in MLB history?(25 Innings)"
    ]

    const answers = [
        ["Jeff Cartejena",
        "Jeff Cartejena",
        "Jeff Cartejena",
        "Jeff Cartejena"
        ],
        ["Boston Red Sox",
        "Chicago White Sox",
        "New York Yankees",
        "Chicago Cubs"
        ],
        ["Dallas Cowboys",
        "Pittsburgh Steelers",
        "New England Patriots",
        "Washington Redskins"
        ],
        ["Phil Ivey",
        "Phil Hellmuth",
        "Doyle Brunson",
        "Johhny Chan"
        ],
        ["Earl Campbell",
        "Cedric Benson",
        "Ricky Williams",
        "Jamaal Charles"
        ],
        ["Secretariat",
        "Sham",
        "Funny Cide",
        "Seabiscuit"
        ],
        ["Ricky Williams",
        "Colt McCoy",
        "Peter Gardere",
        "Earl Campbell"
        ],
        ["22",
        "20",
        "19",
        "21",
        ],
        ["Notre Dame",
        "Florida State",
        "USC",
        "Alabama",
        ],
        ["Walter Payton",
        "Barry Sanders",
        "Jim Brown",
        "Emmit Smith",
        ],
        ["Jose Altuve",
        "Jeff Bagwell",
        "Craig Biggio",
        "Nolan Ryan",
        ],
        ["Colt .45s",
        "Texans",
        "Oilers",
        "Cougars",
        ],
        ["Kevin VanDam",
        "Rick Clunn",
        "Bobby Murray",
        "Larry Nixon",
        ],
        ["Rick Clunn",
        "Randy Howell",
        "Jordan Lee",
        "Kevin VanDam",
        ],
        ["Sammy Sosa",
        "Babe Ruth",
        "Barry Bonds",
        "Hank Aaron",
        ],
        ["Jackie Slater",
        "Emmit Smith",
        "Jerry Rice",
        "Brett Favre"
        ],
        ["Gary Anderson",
        "Jerry Rice",
        "Morten Andersen",
        "George Blanda"
        ],
        ["Lawrence Taylor",
        "Derrick Thomas",
        "Reggie White",
        "Michael Strahan",
        ],
        ["Roger Staubach",
        "Terry Bradshaw",
        "Johnny Unitas",
        "Joe Montana",
        ],
        ["Miami Dolphins",
        "Pittsburg Steelers",
        "New England Patriots",
        "Cleveland Browns"
        ],
        ["Boston Red Sox",
        "Chicago White Sox",
        "New York Yankees",
        "Chicago Cubs"
        ]
    ]
    const correctAnswers = ["Jeff Cartejena",
        "Chicago White Sox",
        "Washington Redskins",
        "Phil Hellmuth",
        "Ricky Williams",
        "Secretariat",
        "Ricky Williams",
        "20",
        "USC",
        "Emmit Smith",
        "Jeff Bagwell",
        "Colt .45s",
        "Rick Clunn",
        "Kevin VanDam",
        "Barry Bonds",
        "Jackie Slater",
        "Morten Andersen",
        "Derrick Thomas",
        "Joe Montana",
        "Miami Dolphins",
        "Chicago White Sox"
        ];
